Clark Nelson

Web Developer and Designer

Portfolio: https://clarknelson.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/clarknelson
Email: mail@clarknelson.com
Phone: 630-310-6686

SUMMARY

I have over five years experience programming responsive web applications. I specialize in front-end development using modern JavaScript frameworks. I would like to improve in databases and network secruity. I believe in simple interfaces that provide powerful functionality.

EDUCATION

DePaul University, Chicago II. Expected May 2016
Bachelor of Science in Computer Science 3.125 GPA

Designation, Chicago II.

Full-stack design bootcamp

Graduated with Recomendation

EXPERIENCE

Developer at Pixl LLC.

June 2015 - January 2016

- Worked with former classmates at Designation.io to design websites for clients
- Developed an enterprise React.js application with team members around the world
- Colaborated closely with design team to establish front-end identities for clients

Freelance Front-end Development

December 2014 - June 2015

- Maintained several WordPress sites while attending school full time
- Worked with a bankruptcy lawyer in Georgia and a commodity trading network.

Intern at Neoteric Design

June 2014 - July 2014

- Developed and designed an internal Ruby on Rails application
- Application was created to track client's progress during website development

Intern at Plum Tree Group

June 2013 - August 2013

- Developerment Intern at a mid sized Marketing agency
- Created a few HTML newsletters and taught teammates about front-end technology

SKILLS

Web Development: HTML5, SCSS, JavaScript, React, Node, Rails
Systems Development: Java, C/C++, Bash, SSH, Linux, Android/iOS
Design: Sketch.app, Typography, Layout, User Experience
Other: Agile Development Practices, Music

OBJECTIVE

I am looking for a full time position in June 2016. It would be nice to work in Chicago but I am open to relocation. I love to constantly learn and get better. Work samples can be found on my website.